A dangerous drive
Switchin’ up the gear
Blazing sunset glow
You and my tears so
Don’t be afraid, no doubts at all
Take my hand cause tonight
We burn to shine yeah
Now hold me tight my dear
In the scars we share
Inside our hearts
The engine’s stained in red
If you remember me
The way I’m in your eyes forever
I’m burning HOT
If I can live life my own way
Turning to ashes ain’t no problem
So tonight in your embrace
Bonnie and Clyde it oh
Not running from it
Flames rising high, I love it
Let me live
I'm burning HOT
Just like
A phoenix soaring across eternal skies
You’re just like
A miracle making me dream again tonight
Once again, my embers glow hot
Sprouting wings
Now hold me tight
Throwing my body into flames
No hesitation, no regrets
It’s all right, we’re ride or die, yeah
The engine’s stained in red
If you remember me
The way I’m in your eyes forever
I’m burning HOT
If I can live life my own way
Turning to ashes ain’t no problem
So tonight in your embrace
Bonnie and Clyde it oh
Not running from it
Flames rising high, I love it
Let me live
I'm burning HOT